Your god can't help you.
Apostle is a horror, mystery film directed by Gareth Evans.
In 1905, a man travels to a remote island in search of his missing sister
who has been kidnapped by a mysterious religious cult.
Thomas Richardson, played by Dan Stevens.
Malcolm Howe, played by Michael Sheen.
Andrea, played by Lucy Boynton.
Quinn, played by Mark Lewis Jones.
Jeremy, played by Bill Milner.
Ffion, played by Kristine Froseth.
Apostle is a 2018 Gothic folk horror film written, directed and edited by Gareth Evans, and starring Dan Stevens,
Lucy Boynton, Mark Lewis Jones, Bill Milner, Kristine Froseth, Paul Higgins and Michael Sheen.
It had its world premiere at Fantastic Fest in September 2018, and
began streaming on Netflix on October 12, 2018.
The story follows a British man as he attempts to rescue
his sister from a cult on a remote island.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of wales, ransom, gore, cult, murder.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.